Wildey "Bud" Kimball Photographs 1959-1980
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Wildey "Bud" Kimball Photographs
1959-1980
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc/ mascref@wsu.edu
PC 121
17 containers 10 linear feet
The Wildey "Bud" Kimball collection consists primarily of aerial photographs, in varying formats, taken by Kimball between 1959 and 1980. The majority of the photographs are from western Washington State. Of particular note are Kimball's detailed aerial color photographs of Mt. St. Helens before and after the May 18, 1980 eruption.
Biographical Note:
Wildey "Bud" Kimball was born in Portland, Oregon on November 23, 1914. He had an early interest in flight, and received his Private Pilot's license on December 20, 1932. He graduated from Stadium High School in Tacoma, WA in 1933. While in college, he became a glider instructor, one of only five certified glider pilots west of the Mississippi River. When World War II broke out, Kimball became a flight instructor at the Twentynine Palms Air Academy in California under contract to the Army. In 1950, Kimball began apprentice training in aerial photography with United Aerial Survey of Sonora, CA. In subsequent years he worked as a flight instructor, an aircraft salesman, a fashion photographer, and a pilot. By 1965, he had logged 9000 hours of flight time in various aircraft. Kimball retired to Ocean Shores, WA.
The Wildey "Bud" Kimball collection consists primarily of aerial photographs, in varying formats, taken by Kimball between 1959 and 1980. While the majority of the photographs are from western Washington state, also included are photographs from a 1966 California/Nevada/Arizona trip and images of Alaskan glaciers from two separate trips in 1972 and 1978.
Of particular note are Kimball's detailed aerial color photographs of Mt. St. Helens before and after the May 18, 1980 eruption. Included is a series taken on May 17th, 1980, approximately 18 hours before the eruption. Kimball's Mt. St. Helens photographs can be found in slide form (series 3), as 24"x24" color transparencies (series 4), as microfiche (series 9), and as a roll of original negative film (series 12: box 17, item 233). Small quantities of St. Helens images can be found in several other series as well.
Where possible, the collection has been left in its original order ascribed to it by its creator. The majority of the collection is sorted by size and type of materials, and then sorted chronologically within those series. For materials where no discernible organization existed, items were generally again sorted by type and then either chronologically or by subject within each category.
Arranged in 13 series:
Series 1: Black and white negatives and prints (7" x7 1/2")
Series 2: Miscellaneous black and white prints
Series 3: Slides
Series 4: Color transparencies; 24 x 24 cm
Series 5: Color and black and white negatives and transparencies, 4" x 5", 2 1/4" x 2 1/4", and 2 1/4" x 3 1/4"
Series 6: 4"x5" color transparencies: 1966 California trip
Series 7: 9" x 9" color transparencies and negatives
Series 8: Miscellaneous negatives and transparencies
Series 9: Microfiche & associated 5" x4 1/4" color transparencies
Series 10: 5" x4 1/4" color transparencies
Series 11: Color prints
Series 12: Rolls of 7" aerial negatives
Series 13: Oversize Prints
These documents were a gift to WSU Libraries MASC from Bud Kimball in 1978 and 1992.
Volcanism -- Washington (State) -- Saint Helens, Mount -- Photographs.; Tacoma (Wash.) -- Photographs.; Saint Helens, Mount (Wash.) -- Eruption, 1980 -- Photographs.; Aerial photographs -- Washington (State) -- 1959-1980.; Negatives -- Washington (State) -- 1959-1980.; Transparencies -- Washington (State) -- 1959-1980.; Washington (State); Tacoma; Environmental Conditions; Photographs
- Black and white aerial negatives and prints (7"x7 1/2"), 1
  Negatives, and prints without negatives interfiled chronologically. Very few negatives with prints but many contact prints from negatives missing in sequence. Identifications taken from negative envelopes.
  - Protection Island, 3/2/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Mountain, 2 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Betty's house, 10 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Jervie-lakefront, 11 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Road-Columbia Gorge, 12 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Narrows Bridge, west end, Tacoma, 3/15/1966; 1-6 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - 48th and South Bridgeport, Tacoma, 7-19 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Steilacoom Outboard, 6/28/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Steilacoom Point, 2 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Steilacoom Ferry dock, 3 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Steilacoom sewer disposal, 4 (Box-folder 1/3)
    (print incl.)
  - Tacoma News Print, 5 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Brookside, new Tacoma cemetery, 6 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Child Treatment Center, 7 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - Oakbrook, 7/8/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Pioneer Sand and gavel, 2,3 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Narrow Lumber Co, 4 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Yacht Harbor, Day Island, 5 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Day Island Marina, 6 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Narrows Marina, 7 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Lumber mill, Day Island, 8 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Titlow Beach Pool, 9 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - 6th Avenue Sewage Disposal, Tacoma, 10 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Toby Jones Rest Home, 11 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Point Defiance Park, 12 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Port of Tacoma, Pier 1, 13-20 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Port of Tacoma, Hylobos Waterway, 7/12/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, 2-3 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, shipyard, 4 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, Pier 1, 5-6 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, Johnnies Dock, 7 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Tideflats, Tacoma Boat Building, 8 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, Pier 7, 9 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, Cheney's, 10-11 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Port of Tacoma, Pier 1, 12 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Tideflats, Sperry Docks, 13-14 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Tideflats, Commings Boat, 15 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - University of Puget Sound, 16 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Allenmore Medical Center, 17 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Gateway Chevrolet, Gig Harbor, 18 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Gig Harbor Lumber, 19 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Gig Harbor Food King, 20 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Joe Hoots, Gig Harbor, 21 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Gig Harbor, 22 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Perking Funeral Home, Gig Harbor, 23 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Power company yards, Gig Harbor, 24 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Gig Harbor Boat Dock, 25 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Wynwood, Gig Harbor, 26 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Gravel pit, Gig Harbor, 27 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Purdy, Washington, 28 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Home, Purdy, 29-30 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Purdy Truck Terminal, 31 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Purdy Trailer Court, 32-33 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - PV2 (airplane), 34 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Crescent Lake Resort, 35-38 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Camping ground, Straits, 39 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - Logging, Straits, 40 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Log dump, Straits, 41 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Trailer camp, Straits, 42 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Clallam Bay, Straits, 43-45 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Sekiu Airstrip, 46-48 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Neah Bay, 49-61 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Port of Tacoma, 62 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Hylobos Marina, 63 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Spanaway Park, 64 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - Beachcrest, 7/17/1966; 1-3 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Ketron Island Marina, 7/18/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Steilacoom Outboard, 2 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - McNeil Island, 3-4 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Spanaway Race Track, 5. (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Army boats, 6. (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Anderson Island, 7 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Ketron Island, 8 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - McNeil Island, 9 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Conrad home, 10 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Marine View Marina (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Fairliner Marina, 12-13 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Hylobos Marina (print), 14 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - George Marvin Oil Co, 15-16 (Box-folder 1/9)
    (print)
  - McNeil Island, 17-26 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Anderson Island, 27 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Neah Bay Island, 28 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - West Passage, 7/20/1966; 1-3 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Bremerton, 4-6 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Lake and airport, 7-8 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Tatoosh Island, 25 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - N.W. Washington coast near Neah Pay, 26-35 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Tatoosh Island, 36-37 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Port Angeles, 38 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Narrows Bridges, 39 (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Tacoma Mall, 7/29/1966; 1-1A. (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Valu-Mart, 3 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Cement Pipe Plant, Center Street, Tacoma, 4 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Highway, Ravenna intersection, 5 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - R.W. Williams Real Estate, 8/24/1966; 1-19 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - R.W. Williams Real Estate, 20-26 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Spanaway Park, 27 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Trailer park, Meridian and 112th, 28-29 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Wilderness School, Puyallup, Washington, 30-32 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - Port of Tacoma, 8/28/1966; 1-19 (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Port of Tacoma, 20-29 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Downtown Tacoma, 30-40 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Downtown Tacoma, 41-52a (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Puyallup Trailer Court, 52-59 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - Puyallup Trailer Court, 60-62 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Springdale Dairy, 65 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Pete Lovely Volkswagen, 66 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Port of Tacoma, 9/25/1966; 1-3 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Point Defiance, 10/10/1966; 1-3 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Dick Magoon Real Estate, 4-29 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Dick Magoon Real Estate, 30-33 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - Port of Tacoma, Manhattan, 10/21/1966; 6-11 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Alumina U. C., Port of Tacoma, 12-14 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Port of Tacoma, Manhattan, 15-20 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - George Marvin, Hylobos, 11/3/1966; 4-7 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Mall, 8-10 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Tacoma Urban Renewal, 11/18/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Big gulch, 50-65 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Picnic Cove, 66-72 (Box-folder 1/23)
  - Washington State Parks, 1/13/1967; 1-20 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Mt. Adams, 12/1/1966; 1 (Box-folder 1/25)
  - Olympics, 1/23/1967; 1 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Fawn Lake, 2-10 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Shelton with Olympics, 11 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Fawn Lake, 12-23 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Federal Way, 2/20/1967; 1-24 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - NE Tacoma shopping center, 25 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - Port of Tacoma, Pier 7, 26-31 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - Browns Point, 3/30/1967; 1-15 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - Unidentified, 16-23 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - Tacoma Mall, 4/1/1967; 1 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Tacoma Mall, 4/2/1967; 14-23 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - HiHo shopping center, 5/6/1967; 7-11 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - Tacoma?, 5/16/1967; 1-4 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - Tacoma?, 15 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - North Tacoma, 5/25/1967; 2-4 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Unidentified, 8 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Unidentified, 19 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Weyerhaeuser, Green River plant, 30 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Kent, Washington, 31 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Boeing Plant, Paine Field, 6/27/1967; 1-2 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Yacht Club and canal, Seattle, 3 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Sewer disposal, Seattle, 4 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Pier 91, Seattle, 5 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Lake Union, Seattle, 6 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - University of Washington, 7 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Seattle Freeway, Lake Union Bridge, 8 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Seattle waterfront, 9 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Boeing, Kent, 10 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Unidentified, 11-12 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Port of Tacoma, 13-18 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Boeing, Kent, 20-23 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Boeing, Auburn, 24-28 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Dr. Marlatt(ocean shoreline), 6/30/1967; 1-9 (Box-folder 2/35)
  - Unidentified, 10-14 (Box-folder 2/35)
  - Unidentified, 12/1/1967; 1-2 (Box-folder 2/36)
  - Unidentified, 7/17/1968; 6-9 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Mossyrock Camp, 10 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Unidentified, 11 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Dam aerials, 17,19,23,27,28 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Unidentified, 34,35,37,46 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Steilacoom, 50-51 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Fish hatchery, 7/27/1968; 6-13 (Box-folder 2/38)
  - Cowlitz Boat Race, 19-23 (Box-folder 2/38)
  - Unidentified, 7/28/1968; 16 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - Unidentified, 21 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - Unidentified, 7/30/1968; 55 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Unidentified, 78 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Tacoma from 6th and N. Pearl, 79-80 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Tacoma from Salmon Beach, 84-85 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Tacoma Mall, 102 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Unidentified, 103 (Box-folder 2/40)
  - Tacoma, 9/2/1968; 1-44 (Box-folder 2/41)
  - Guig Harbor, Puget Sound, 3/10/1969; 16 (Box-folder 2/42)
  - Weyerhaeuser, 3/11/1969; 16 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - Unidentified, 107,110,121,124,159,161,167 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - Weyerhaeuser, 170-172 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - S.W. Tacoma, 173 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - Tacoma, Bantz and 19th, 174 (Box-folder 2/43)
- Miscellaneous black and white prints, 2
  Arranged by subject.
  - Airplanes (Box-folder 3/44)
  - Bremerton (Box-folder 3/45)
  - Mountains (Box-folder 3/46)
  - Mount Rainier (Box-folder 3/47)
  - Olympia- Capitol Building (Box-folder 3/48)
  - Salt Lake City- Mormon Tabernacle (Box-folder 3/49)
  - Seascapes (Box-folder 3/50)
  - Seattle (Box-folder 3/51)
  - Tacoma aerials (Box-folder 3/52)
  - Unidentified aerials (Tacoma?) (Box-folder 3/53)
  - Unidentified and miscellaneous nonaerials (Box-folder 3/54)
- Aerial photographs, 3; Slides
  Arranged by subjects, then chronologically within subject.
  - Central Washington, undated (Box-folder 4/55)
  - Farm, unidentified, undated (Box-folder 4/56)
  - Mt. Baker, June 1975-September 1978 (Box-folder 4/57)
  - Mt. Rainier, May 1973-October 1980 (Box-folder 4/58)
  - Mt. St. Helens
    - 1959, 1963, 1973 (Box-folder 4/59)
    - 1978-1979 (Box-folder 4/60)
    - (selected), March 25 1980-April 2 1980 (Box-folder 4/61)
    - March 25 1980 (Box-folder 4/62)
    - March 27 1980 (Box-folder 4/63)
    - April 2 1980, April 8, 1980 (Box-folder 4/64)
    - April 30 1980 (Box-folder 4/65)
    - May 17 1980 (Box-folder 4/66)
    - May 18 1980 (Box-folder 4/67)
    - June 3 1980 (Box-folder 4/68)
    - June 6 1980 (Box-folder 4/69)
    - June 19 1980 (Box-folder 4/70)
    - June 20 1980 (Box-folder 4/71)
    - July 6, 8, 9 1980 (Box-folder 4/72)
    - July 22 1980 (Box-folder 4/73)
    - September 4 1980 (Box-folder 4/74)
    - (clean-up), September 22 1980 (Box-folder 4/75)
    - (clean-up), November 18 1980 (Box-folder 4/76)
    - Mt. St. Helens Erupts, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 4/77)
      Purchased slide set, not Kimball.
- Aerial Photographs: Washington State mountains, 4; Color transparencies; 24 x 24 cm.
  - Mt. Adams
    - July 27 1976 (Box-folder 4/78)
    - January 13 1977 (Box-folder 4/79)
  - Mt. Rainier
    - July 23 1976 (Box-folder 4/80)
    - July 27 1976 (Box-folder 4/81)
    - July 29 1976 (Box-folder 4/82)
    - September 27 1976 (Box-folder 4/83)
    - October 20 1976 (Box-folder 4/84)
    - January 13 1977 (Box-folder 4/85)
    - January 25 1977 (Box-folder 4/86)
    - January 27 1977 (Box-folder 4/87)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 4/88)
  - Mt. St. Helens
    - September 1976 (Box-folder 4/89)
    - January 13 1977 (Box-folder 4/90)
    - March 25 1980 (Box-folder 4/91)
    - April 2 1980 (Box-folder 4/92)
    - April 30 1980 (Box-folder 4/93)
    - May 17 1980 (Box-folder 4/94)
    - June 19 1980 (Box-folder 4/95)
    - June 20 1980 (Box-folder 4/96)
    - July 6 1980 (Box-folder 4/97)
  - Mt. Si
    - Undated (Box-folder 4/98)
- Color and black and white negatives and transparencies, 4"x5", 2 1/4"x2 1/4", and 2 1/4"x 3 1/4", arranged by subject, 5
  - Aerials-rivers, 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/99)
  - Aerials-Seattle, 1963; 4"x5" color negatives (11). 4"x5" transparency (1) (Box-folder 5/700)
  - Aerials-Tacoma, 4"x5" B&W negatives (9). 4"x5" color negatives (37). 2 1/4" color negatives (5). 4"x5" color transparencies (19). (Box-folder 5/101)
  - Aerials-Tacoma, July, 1964; 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/102)
  - Aerials-Tacoma, 1965; 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/103)
  - Airplanes, 4"x5" color negative (1). 4"x5" B&W negatives (4). 2 1/4" B&W negatives (18). 2 1/4" color negatives (14). 2 1/4"x3 1/4" color negatives (5). 2 1/4"x3 1/4" B&W negatives (5). (Box-folder 5/104)
  - Airports, 4"x5" color negatives (11). 4"x5" color transparencies (3). (Box-folder 5/105)
  - Allenmore Hospital, Tacoma, 2 1/4" color negatives (Box-folder 5/106)
  - Boats, 2 1/4" color negatives (57). 4"x5" color negatives (2). (Box-folder 5/107)
  - Bremerton, 4"x5" B&W negatives (Box-folder 5/108)
  - Buildings, business and miscellaneous, 4"x5" color negatives (13). 2 1/4" color negatives (2). (Box-folder 5/109)
  - Capitol Building, Olympia, 4"x5" color transparencies (3). 2 1/4" color negatives (9). (Box-folder 5/110)
  - Cats, 2 1/4" color negatives (Box-folder 5/111)
  - Cloth backgrounds, 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/112)
  - Clouds, 4"x5" color negatives (2). 2 1/4" color negatives (1). (Box-folder 5/113)
  - Cowlitz River, 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/114)
  - Daffodil Parade, Tacoma, 1965; 4"x5" color negatives (8). 2 1/4" color negatives (82). (Box-folder 5/115)
  - Executive Aviation, 4"x5" color negatives (30). 4"x5" B&W negatives (33). 2 1/4" color negatives (54). 2 1/4" B&W negatives (60) (Box-folder 5/116)
  - Federal Way, 4"x5" color negatives (1). 4"x5" color transparencies (4). (Box-folder 5/117)
  - Fireworks, 2 1/4"x3 1/4" color negatives (Box-folder 5/118)
  - Flowers, 4"x5" color negatives (2). 2 1/4" color negatives (7). 2 1/4"x3 1/4" color negatives (5). (Box-folder 5/119)
  - Gig Harbor, 4"x5" B&W negatives (Box-folder 5/120)
  - Highways, 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/121)
  - Logging, 4"x5" color transparencies (Box-folder 5/122)
  - McNeil Island Penitentiary, 4"x5" transparencies (Box-folder 5/123)
  - Mercantile buildings, 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 5/124)
  - Mountains, 4"x5" color transparencies (3). 4"x5" B&W negatives (1). 2 1/4" color negatives (53). (Box-folder 5/125)
  - Mt. Rainier, 4"x5" color transparencies (12). 4"x5" color negatives (1). (Box-folder 5/126)
  - North Fort Lewis, 4"x5" color transparencies (Box-folder 5/127)
  - Olympia Brewery, 4"x5" color transparencies (6). 4"x5" B&W negatives (2). (Box-folder 5/128)
  - Oswald Flying Service, Tacoma, 4"x5" color negatives (3). 2 1/4" B&W negatives (16). (Box-folder 5/129)
  - Port of Tacoma, 2 1/4"x3 1/4" B&W negative (Box-folder 5/130)
  - Puyallup Fairgrounds, 4"x5" color transparencies (6). 4"x5" B&W negatives (13). (Box-folder 5/131)
  - Rotor wing aircraft, 4"x5" color negatives (3). 4"x5" color transparencies (1). 4"x5" B&W negatives (35). 2 1/4" color negatives (46). (Box-folder 6/132)
  - Seascapes, 4"x5" color transparencies (2). 2 1/4" color negatives (16). 2 1/4"x3 1/4" color negatives (3). (Box-folder 6/133)
  - Seattle International Raceways, 4"x5" color negatives (Box-folder 6/134)
  - Steilacoom Outboard-Saulter's Point, 4"x5" B&W negatives (2). 2 1/4" color negatives (15). 2 1/4" B&W negatives (11). 2 1/4"x3 1/4" color negatives (8). (Box-folder 6/135)
  - Tacoma Boat Building Co, 4"x5" color negatives (2).4"x5" B&W negatives (14). (Box-folder 6/136)
  - Tacoma Narrows Bridge, 2 1/4" color negatives (Box-folder 6/137)
  - Washington D.C, 2 1/4"x3 1/4" B&W negatives (Box-folder 6/138)
  - Whitakers Chalet, 4"x5" color negatives (3). 2 1/4" color negatives (2). (Box-folder 6/139)
  - Unidentified and miscellaneous, 4"x5" color negatives (21). 4"x5" B&W negatives (1). 4"x5" color transparencies (21). 2 1/4" color negatives (139) with a few prints. (Box-folder 6/140)
- 1966 California trip of 4"x5" color transparencies (aerials) with descriptions, 6
  - Crater Lake, 1 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Pierce Ferry on Lake Mead, 2 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Stateline, Nevada, 3 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Stateline, Nevada, 4 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Sacramento, California Municipal Airport, 5 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Recreation area on Colorado River, 6 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Grape vineyard near Thermal, California, 7 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Recreation area on Salton Sea, 8 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Central Oregon lumber mill, near Redmond, Oregon, 9 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - New Alfalfa ranch near Kingman, Arizona, 10 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Indian farm lands near Klamath Falls, Oregon, 11 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Las Vegas, Nevada, 12 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - State park at Coloma, California, 13 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Hoover Dam, Lake Mead, 14 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Hoover Dam, Lake Mead, 15 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Logging road, Siskiyou range, 16 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Homes west of Indio, California, 17 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Reno, Nevada, 18 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Crystal Bay, Lake Tahoe, Nevada, 19 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Donner Lake, California, 20 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Lake Tahoe, Nevada, 21 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Subdivisions near Merced, California, 22 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Mt. Vernon, Washington, 23 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Boulder City, Nevada, 24 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Las Vegas, Nevada Municipal Airport, 25 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Lumber mills between Cottage Grove and Roseburg, Oregon, 26 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Grand Canyon National Park Airport, 27 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Chowchilla, California, 28 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Chowchilla, California, 29 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Irrigated field near Blyth, California, 30 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Cattle ranch near Shasta, California, 31 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Cattle ranch near Shasta, California, 32 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Gig Harbor, Washington, 33 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Central Oregon farmlands, 34 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Columbia River near Hood River, Oregon, 35 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Volcanic cone lookout station south of Bend, Oregon, 36 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - State owned camp ground on Salton Sea, 37 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Homes in Salton Sea development, 38 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Mortmar, California on Salton Sea, 39 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Irrigated farm in Imperial Valley, 40 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Sawmill near Roseburg, Oregon, 41 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Willamette Valley hop farm, 42 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Reno, Nevada Municipal Airport, 43 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Cattle country, Montague, California, 44 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Henderson, Nevada, 45 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Laguna Dam on Colorado River, 46 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - All American Canal near Yuma, Arizona, 47 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - All American Canal, 48 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Ranch in Imperial Valley, 49 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Airport at South Lake Tahoe, 50 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Colorado River near Blythe, California, 51 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Siskiyou range near Yreka, California, 52 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Recreation area on Colorado River, 53 (Box-folder 6/141)
  - Unidentified (Box-folder 6/141)
- 9"x9" color aerial transparencies and negatives arranged by subject alphabetically, 7
  - Aberdeen, Washington, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/142)
  - Devereaux Lake, color negatives (Box-folder 7/143)
  - Elwa, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/144)
  - Enumclaw, Weyerhaeuser Plant, color transparency (Box-folder 7/145)
  - Hoquiam, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/146)
  - McCleary, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/147)
  - Malaspina Glacier, Alaska, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/148)
  - Mt. Adams, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/149)
  - Mt. Rainier, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/150-153)
  - Mt. St. Helens, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/154)
  - Mountains, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/155)
  - Nalley Valley, Tacoma, B&W negative (Box-folder 7/156)
  - Nuclear Power Plant, color negatives (6). color transparency (1) (Box-folder 7/157)
  - Ocean Shores, color transparency (Box-folder 7/158)
  - Open pit mine, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/159)
  - Port of Tacoma, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/160)
  - Protection Island, Black and white negatives (Box-folder 7/161)
  - Seattle, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/162)
  - Sunsets, color transparencies (Box-folder 7/163)